Who killed who?
Manhattan Murder Mystery is a comedy, mystery film directed by Woody Allen.
A middle-aged couple suspects foul play when their
neighbor's wife suddenly drops dead.
Larry Lipton, played by Woody Allen.
Carol Lipton, played by Diane Keaton.
Paul House, played by Jerry Adler.
Ted, played by Alan Alda.
Marcia Fox, played by Anjelica Huston.
Lilian House, played by Lynn Cohen.
Manhattan Murder Mystery is a 1993 American black comedy mystery film directed by Woody Allen, which he
wrote with Marshall Brickman, and starring Allen, Alan Alda, Anjelica Huston, and Diane Keaton.
The film centers on a married couple's investigation
of the death of their neighbor's wife.
The film began as an early draft of Annie Hall,
which Allen co-wrote with Brickman.
Eventually, the script evolved and principal photography
took place in 1992, in the titular city.
It was released in August 1993 to positive reviews.
Keaton was nominated for a Golden Globe Award for Best
Actress – Motion Picture Comedy or Musical.
This film marked the eighth and final collaboration between Allen and Keaton.
The film explores themes of investigation, dark
comedy, neighbor, manhattan, new york city.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.